<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><GameData>	<LocalizedText>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_MAP_NAME' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Upplärningskarta</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_MAP_DESCRIPTION' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>En karta som används enbart för handledningen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TECH_DAWN_OF_CIVILIZATION_NAME' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Civilisationens gryning</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TECH_DAWN_OF_CIVILIZATION_DESCRIPTION' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Nödvändig kunskap för civilisationens gryning</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TECH_DAWN_OF_CIVILIZATION_QUOTE_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In the beginning, the earth was without form. And void. And then the sun shone upon the sleeping earth. Into this swirling maelstrom of fire air and water, the first stirrings of life appeared.</Text>		</Replace>		<!---->		<!-- BUTTON TEXT -->		<!---->		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_OK' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>OK</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_SHOW_ME' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Visa mig hur</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_DISMISS' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You are dismissed</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_ASSISTANCE_APPRECIATED' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your assistance is appreciated</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_CONTINUE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Fortsätt</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_GET_STARTED' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Låt oss börja</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_AGREED' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Agreed</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_VERY_GOOD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Mycket bra</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_BUTTON_TELL_ME_MORE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Berätta mer</Text>		</Replace>		<!---->		<!-- ADVISOR TEXT -->		<!---->		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>RÅDGIVARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_MESSAGE_INTRO' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>As your advisor I am qualified to assist you in all matters related to ruling our civilization.[NEWLINE]If you do not require my service, you can dismiss me to attend to other matters.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Greetings My Liege! As your personal advisor, I am qualified to assist you in all matters related to ruling our civilization. I am at your service.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>All great civilizations begin with a great city, and our Settlers have found an ideal location. Order them to found a new city here.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_3' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Well done! You have founded your first city. From these roots your civilization will grow to stand the test of time. Now you must nurture and protect what you have created.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_4' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Security is of great importance. There are barbaric tribes near us who want nothing more than to pillage and plunder what is ours.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_5' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Direct the production efforts of this city to train Warriors to deal with this impending threat.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_6' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Training has begun, but it will be some time before our new Warriors are ready. There are no further matters to attend to right now.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_7' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your city is busy training Warriors for its defense, but a great civilization cannot thrive on military might alone. We have people talented in the ways of science and discovery. You should employ them in researching new technologies which will advance our civilization.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_8' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Wise decision, Your Majesty. This technology will let us better extract the riches from the earth and increase [ICON_Production] Production in our cities. I will let you know when we have finished our research.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_9' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, hostile Barbarians have been seen near our [ICON_Capital] Capital. If left alone they are sure to attack our people and pillage our lands. Your newly trained Warriors await your orders to attack!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_10' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our Warriors were victorious! They fought well to defend our people against this threat. However, the Barbarians are still envious of our civilization. We should be prepared in case they return in greater force.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_11' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are other matters, Your Excellency.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_12' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Since Warrior training is complete, it is time to assign a new production task to the city.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_13' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The lands surrounding our city could be bountiful if we develop them. We should train Builders to create improvements to the lands within our borders.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_14' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are mysteries that await us outside our borders in the uncharted lands beyond. The only way to find out is to explore.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_14_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vid spelets början blir din stad och de närmaste landområdena synliga, men allt som ligger längre bort (illustrerat på kartan som tomt pergament) är delar av världen som du ännu inte utforskat.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_16_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Krigarenheter har ett [ICON_Movement] Förflyttningsvärde på 2.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Den blåfärgade konturlinjen som visas på markerna runt den markerade enheten visar den längsta sträckan som enheten kan flytta under en och samma omgång.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_17_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Öppen terräng, som till exempel Slätter och Gräsmark, förbrukar bara 1 [ICON_Movement] Förflyttningspoäng, medan svårare terräng, som Skog och Kullar, kommer förbruka 2 eller fler [ICON_Movement] Förflyttningspoäng. Flytta Krigar-enheten till den upplysta rutan genom att högerklicka på den.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_17b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FLYTTA KRIGARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_17b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>HÖGERKLICKA på den upplysta rutan för att flytta din Krigare.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_15' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, our Warriors have discovered a small Tribal Village whose inhabitants are welcoming and friendly. Shall we investigate it and send the Warriors to speak with them?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_18_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Att utforska Stambyar kan ge din civilisation en av flera olika omedelbara belöningar, som ytterligare [ICON_Citizen] Befolkning i din stad, eller en summa [ICON_Gold] Guld. Det är en god strategi att utforska så många Stambyar som möjligt.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_20_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FLYTTA KRIGARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_20_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>För att utforska en Stamby, flytta in en av dina enheter i Stambyns ruta. Försök flytta din Krigarenhet dit nu.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_16' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It appears that the Tribal Villagers are also harassed by the Barbarians. They are impressed by our culture, and have decided to join us in the fight!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_17' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Good news indeed! They are skillful Scouts and wily travelers. They can move faster than our Warriors, making them ideal for exploring the surrounding lands, but they are not as strong in combat. They eagerly await your orders.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_21_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Lägg märke till att Spejarenheten har en [ICON_Movement] Förflyttningspoäng på 3, vilket tillåter den att flytta en längre sträcka än andra enheter. Flytta Spejarenheten mot en outforskad del av kartan.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_18' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Scouts are excellent at exploring, but they are not as strong in combat as our Warriors. It is better to have them focus on exploration and survival rather than fighting our enemies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_19' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A team of Builders has finished their training in our city. They are ready to work on improving the surrounding lands. There are ideal locations for the growing of [ICON_Food] Food to support our populace. Constructing a Farm there would increase our yield from those lands.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_22_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Byggare kan konstruera många olika typer av förbättringar på våra landområden. Vilken typ av förbättring de kan bygga på en viss ruta avgörs ofta av rutans typ av terräng. Slätter och Gräsmark är idealiska för Bondgårdar, vilket hjälper till att öka [ICON_Citizen] Befolkningen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_23_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FLYTTA BYGGARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_23_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Flytta din Byggare till det upplysta Slättområdet intill din stad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_24_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>KONSTRUERA BONDGÅRD</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_24_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Konstruera en Bondgårdsförbättring här genom att klicka på knappen ”Bygg förbättring: Bondgård” bredvid enhetspanelen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_25_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Att konstruera en Bondgård här har ökat avkastningen av [ICON_Food] Mat på den här rutan från 1 [ICON_Food] Mat per omgång till 2. Mängden [ICON_Food] Mat som din stad genererar avgör hur snabbt stadens Befolkning växer och ger dig fler [ICON_Citizen] Invånare som kan jobba på landrutorna. Mer [ICON_Food] Mat ger snabbare tillväxt.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_26_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Byggare kan konstruera upp till 3 förbättringar innan arbetsstyrkan är förbrukad. Det kvarvarande antalet användningar visas i Enhetspanelen. Den här Byggar-enheten har förbrukat en i arbetsstyrkan genom att bygga Bondgården, och har nu 2 kvar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_20' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, it is once again time to choose where to direct the production efforts of our city. Your leadership is without equal and our civilization continues to thrive. Shall we construct a Monument to honor our civilization's growing greatness?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_MESSAGE_SELECT_END_TURN' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are no more pressing issues at this time. Shall we continue with our duties?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our explorers on the frontier have discovered a Barbarian camp. This is the source of the Barbarians threatening our region. We must destroy this stronghold, or they will continue to plague us.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_3' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>I would advise you to use caution. The Barbarian camp is heavily defended by their best troops and will be hard to take. We should send an assault force of multiple military units to ensure victory.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_MESSAGE_BARBARIAN_CAMP_DISCOVERED_C' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In developing your military, it is always a good strategy to diversify. Not all units are created equal, some are better against others, and have abilities that separate them from the rest.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_124_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In developing your military, it is always a good strategy to diversify. Not all units are created equal, some are better against others, and have abilities that separate them from the rest.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_7' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our explorers have spotted another friendly Tribal Village. I suggest we send our Scouts to investigate it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_8' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A good city can become a great city through careful planning. Deciding where to place a city district is an important decision. Be sure to pick a location best suited to reap the most benefit.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_4' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Excellency, I am happy to announce that because of our city's prosperity, our [ICON_Citizen] Population has grown!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_MESSAGE_CITY_POPULATION_CHANGED_B' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[ICON_Citizen] Befolkningsstorleken i din första stad har växt från 1 till 2. Så länge som staden får tillräckligt med mat och dess invånare är nöjda kommer den att fortsätta att växa. Stadens [ICON_Citizen] Invånare arbetar på de omgivande rutorna, och förbättringar bidrar till högre avkastningar. Större [ICON_Citizen] Befolkning bidrar till snabbare [ICON_Science] Forskning, snabbare [ICON_Production] Produktion, och snabbare [ICON_Culture] Kulturell tillväxt.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_125_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[ICON_Citizen] Befolkningsstorleken i din första stad har växt från 1 till 2. Så länge som staden får tillräckligt med mat och dess invånare är nöjda kommer den att fortsätta att växa. Stadens [ICON_Citizen] Invånare arbetar på de omgivande rutorna, och förbättringar bidrar till högre avkastningar. Större [ICON_Citizen] Befolkning bidrar till snabbare [ICON_Science] Forskning, snabbare [ICON_Production] Produktion, och snabbare [ICON_Culture] Kulturell tillväxt.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_MESSAGE_CITY_POPULATION_CHANGED_C' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det är alltid en god strategi att inte bara grunda nya städer för att expandera riket, utan också få dem att växa.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_126_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det är alltid en bra strategi att inte bara grunda nya städer för att expandera riket, utan att också få dessa städer att växa.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_MESSAGE_NATURAL_WONDER_REVEALED' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In Civilization VI, you can get Eureka Moments that boost your technology research through in game achievements. This Eureka Moment was gained by discovering a natural wonder. Other achievements could be winning a battle with a specific unit or constructing a building. Achieving these greatly accelerates your technological progress.</Text>		</Replace>		<!-- Listener lines -->		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Through exploration we have discovered a natural wonder of the world. There is no doubt that it could provide a great benefit to the one who settles the lands surrounding it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Rekognosceringsenheter som Spejaren är unika på så vis att de kan få erfarenhet av att utforska och upptäcka delar av världen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_3' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The workforce of our Builder unit has been expended. We will need to train more Builders to continue building improvements on the lands surrounding our cities.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_4' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Enacting new policies in our government can be of great benefit. Our people await your decree.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_5' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The opportunity has arrived for a change into a new and more powerful system of government. Let us strengthen our identity and enact more policies to govern our people.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_6' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have the opportunity to develop a formal Trade Route between two cities. A Trader unit is required to establish such a route, which would be very beneficial for our economy.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_7' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In addition to bringing riches to our civilization, this Trade Route will gradually develop Roads between our cities. Roads allow our units to no longer be impaired by the difficult terrain through which they pass.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_9' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This military unit has proven themselves. From the experience they have gained in combat they are eligible to be granted a promotion. How will you award these brave souls?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_10' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The combat achievements of this unit have become legendary, and worthy of a name unique to them. With what title shall we honor them?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_11' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The health of this unit is very low and in danger of being lost. Allowing a unit to take a break from combat and rest will allow it to heal over time.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_12' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It is best to use caution when moving close to enemy units. Doing so will often force the unit to be in the enemy's 'zone of control', restricting its movement.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_13' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My liege, our city would do well with some farms or other improvements. I suggest we train a Builder soon.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_14' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our Builders have been idle. Perhaps we should direct their efforts to improving the lands around our city.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_15' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our capital flourishes! But I think it is time that we begin establishing roots elsewhere. Perhaps we should train a Settler.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_16' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My liege, we have an Envoy at our disposal. We can use the Envoy to gain favor with a city-state. Becoming friendly with a city-state neighbor can be greatly beneficial to our civilization.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_17' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our City-State neighbors have made a request of us. If we can impress them, I think they will reward us handsomely.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_18' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>I'm afraid I must report that we are bankrupt. It is imperative that we do whatever we can to ease ourselves of this debt. May I suggest we disband some of our military?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_19' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your grace, I must warn you that some of the improved lands around our city have been pillaged. We should find those responsible and ensure no more damage can be done.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_20' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have recently gained advanced knowledge in city planning. Creating districts in our cities can be much more powerful and lucrative than simple improvements like Farms and Mines.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_21' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our military has learned the way of combining two military units into larger scale Corps. These Corps units are much more powerful than their singular counterparts.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_22' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our military now is trained in the way of combining three military units into a single Army, much larger and more powerful than a Corps unit.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_23' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Grace, we have obtained greater knowledge in the art of building static fortifications. Building Walls around our cities will not only make them stronger against a foreign invader, but will also allow them to bombard nearby enemies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_24' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your grace! The enemy is at our gates, and this city is surrounded and under siege. Supplies and food cannot get through, and our city cannot heal its wounds. It is paramount that we break this encirclement.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_25' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>An enemy is in range of our city. Order the city garrison to conduct a ranged attack against the invaders.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_26' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It is important to keep a close eye on our neighbors, and our people may be able to help. Listen carefully, for they are sometimes privy to more information than we are.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_27' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My liege, we are beginning to attract the attention of the Great People of the world. Of course, there are other leaders vying for their attention, too.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_28' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The more specialized districts we construct, the more we will draw in specialized Great People to share their talents with our civilization. I advise that we continue to build these.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_29' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A famous artist is inspired by our civilization, and has come to our lands to create great works of art. I suggest we find somewhere to house these masterpieces immediately.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_30' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This writer has been inspired by our civilization, and comes to our lands to create great works of writing. I suggest we find somewhere to house these masterpieces immediately.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_31' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our populace has attracted a Great Prophet to our lands! Send this most holy person to our Holy Site and rejoice, for the time has come to found a religion for ourselves.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_32' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This musician is inspired by our civilization, and has come to our land to create great musical works. I suggest we find somewhere to house these masterpieces immediately.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_33' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our civilization's attention to the naval arm of our military has given rise to a Great Admiral among our ranks. When deployed wisely among our ships we are sure to have a distinct advantage in battle.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_34' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our civilization's dedication to military affairs has given rise to a Great General among our troops. When used wisely in the field, generals can change the tide of battle in our favor.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_35' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A great merchant has come to our civilization! Each one has a unique talent which will help our economy flourish.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_36' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our dedication to the ways of science has attracted a great scientist to our civilization! I am certain we will be able to use them to benefit future scientific developments.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_37' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Constructing wonders of the world not only is a remarkable display of our empire's greatness, they have other benefits as well. Remember, other civilizations may also be competing in this endeavor, and there can only be one of each type in the world.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_38' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Just as our citizens have faith in your leadership, so they are beginning to have faith in a higher power. I think it is wise to cultivate this new way of thinking - perhaps there is some benefit to be gained.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_39' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The number of faithful has grown, and it is time for us to define our beliefs. Let us choose a pantheon to worship.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_40' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My liege, we have the ability to train religious missionaries to begin spreading our great religion to foreign lands.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_41' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your majesty, I believe that we may benefit from recruiting an apostle to spread our religion. These holy people are quite powerful in the ways of conversion.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_42' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>All other religions in the world are a threat to our faith. We can recruit Inquisitors to purge the heretics from our cities.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_43' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Excellency, I feel it is time to build some Neighborhoods for our growing populous. We should build these on our most beautiful lands - near natural wonders, or perhaps by the Coast.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_44' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My liege, all of our military has been destroyed and we are completely defenseless. Training military units is of utmost importance if we are to survive.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_45' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our explorers have spotted another friendly Tribal Village. I suggest we send a Scout to investigate.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_46' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, keep your allies close and your enemies closer. We are now able to recruit a Spy who could help us better understand what it is that our neighbors do… On a more covert level.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_50' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Some resources, like this one, can be harvested. This will remove the resource in exchange for an immediate gain.  But once it is removed, it will not come back.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_51' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi har upptäckt en stadsstat! Att etablera diplomatisk kontakt med dem skulle säkert vara gynnsamt för vårt rike. Kanske vi borde skicka dem ett sändebud…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_52' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are several different types of City-States, and each may provide different benefits in return for our friendship. Our government, over time, will allow us to earn envoys to grow these relationships.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_53' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have trained our first ranged unit, capable of hitting enemies from afar, while out of the range of hand-to-hand combat.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_54' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A siege unit! This will surely be useful if we choose to engage in a city attack.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_55' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We are now skilled in the construction of walls to protect our cities. In addition to providing protection from invaders, they are also excellent vantage points to bombard enemies with ranged attacks.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_56' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The enemy has surrounded the city and we are under siege. We must break this blockade or we will not be able to reinforce the garrison and repair our defenses.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_57' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My liege, this city has great defenses. With enough force, and the right military, I think we can take it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_58' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your majesty, there are times when peace is not the better option. I think we now have good reason to show our military might, but it is a careful decision that you must make alone.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_59' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It is a difficult world to face alone, but if I may, I do believe that one of our neighbors has proven worthy. Shall we extend the hand of friendship to them?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_60' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your excellency, I feel it is time that we send a diplomatic delegation to those around us. This will allow us to sow the seeds of friendship, and perhaps give us a better insight as to what these other people may be doing.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_61' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>I have good news! If we wish it, I think we may have an ally amongst our neighbors. This could come in handy if we ever find ourselves in need of help.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_62' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Do not distress, my liege. There are those out there who cannot be pleased, no matter what. It is important to remember what you stand for, and if the time comes… to fight for it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_63' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My liege, I must warn you that denouncing other civilizations will have long and lasting consequences. It is important to think carefully on these matters.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_64' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Though it appears as if we may have offended someone, do not fret. There will always be other leaders with different ideas than our own.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_65' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It seems that our choices have won favor with one of our neighbors. But everyone has their own agenda, and I am sure that someone else may be watching us warily.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_66' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your grace, If I may, I think it is time that we begin exploring what is beyond our shores. It may be that our land units would be fit for this opportunity.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_67' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It isn't just our lands that can be improved, but our waterways as well. I suggest we search for opportunities to exploit the resources along the shores.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_68' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>I think we may have an opportunity to convince the followers of another religion of the error of their ways. Shall we seize this opportunity?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_69' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Foreign proselytizers have been seeking audience with our citizens. I must advise that we do something about this threat to our holy lands. Perhaps we should launch an inquisition.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_70' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Neighborhoods with higher appeal will house more citizens, whereas neighborhoods built by marsh, airports, or rainforest are not going to be very populated at all.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_71' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our treasury is filled with gold, and I think it could be wise to make an investment. Perhaps we could expand our military.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_72' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have not yet constructed a Holy Site, and the great prophet that we have attracted to our city has nowhere to go. Let's construct one!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_73' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our populace has attracted a Great Prophet to our lands! Send this most holy person to Stonehenge and rejoice, for the time has come to found a religion for ourselves.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_74' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A Great Engineer has come to our civilization, ready to work hard to advance our infrastructure. Each has a different talent, but all of them can improve our cities in some way.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_75' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We now have the ability to build a Spaceport. If we further our research, we may be able to unlock the mysteries of the stars.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_76' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have uncovered a way to increase our farming output. To tap into this potential, I suggest we try to maintain two adjacent farms to each plot of farmland.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_77' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have furthered our agricultural technology yet again! Each farm that we build next to another will increase the output of both - I suggest we do this as often as possible.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_78' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Times have changed, and the era of diplomatic delegations has passed. It is important that we now establish Embassies with our friends and allies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_79' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This earth is a gift, and it is important that we protect it. I recommend we establish a National Park. It may even attract tourists!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_80' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It isn't simply seagulls that flock to our shores now. If we build a Seaside Resort, we may be able to benefit from this new attraction to the ocean.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_81' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Though our own people are quite skilled, we can always benefit by learning from others. Perhaps we should look into beginning a Research Agreement with one of our neighbors.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_82' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A Relic! If we can house this for our people to see, I am certain that it will attract more of the faithful to our lands.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_83' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It appears we have become quite a popular attraction to the people of the world. I wonder how many more tourists will travel through our borders…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_84' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You are a brave and mighty conqueror! I have great faith that you will soon rule all of the lands before us.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_85' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our religion spreads throughout the lands. It is a great joy to see so many people embracing what we know to be true. Though, there are still more who have yet to see the light.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_86' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Though our population grows, there is little room for our newest citizens. We should find a way to add more housing to this city.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_87' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your grace, I worry about the happiness of our citizens. I would advise that we investigate a means of increasing their contentment.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_88' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our people have discovered that they have a particular, useful skill that I think we should explore. If we begin construction on this new district now, I believe we will have it completed in no time at all.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_89' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Alas, all of this time that we spend at war is taking a toll on our people. I see pain in their eyes, and our productivity has reached record lows.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_LISTENER_90' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The building of an Archeological Museum will allow us to train Archeologists. There is so much to learn from the world, and they will help us gain this knowledge.</Text>		</Replace>		<!---->		<!-- META TEXT -->		<!---->		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_1_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>MARKERA NYBYGGAREN</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_1_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på Nybyggar-enheten för att välja den.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_8_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>AVSLUTA OMGÅNG</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_8_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det finns inga fler beslut att fatta under den här omgången, så klicka på knappen ”Nästa omgång” för att fortsätta.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_11a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Uppgifter som måste färdigställas innan du kan avsluta din omgång kommer visas i meddelandepanelen i nedre högra delen av skärmen.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Eftersom produktionen är klar i den här staden får du en påminnelse om att du måste välja någonting nytt att tillverka innan du kan avsluta din omgång.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_11_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>ÅTGÄRDER KRÄVS</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_11_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på ”Välj Produktion” för att välja nästa tillverkningsuppdrag.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_33b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>ÅTGÄRDER KRÄVS</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_33b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Forskning måste väljas innan omgången kan avslutas.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_13a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>En Byggarenhet har lagts till i stadens Produktionskö. Det kommer ta flera omgångar innan utbildningen av den är klar. Eftersom det inte finns några fler beslut att fatta under den här omgången, så visas knappen ”Nästa omgång”.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_13_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>AVSLUTA OMGÅNG</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_13_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på knappen ”Nästa omgång” för att fortsätta.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_19_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>AVSLUTA OMGÅNG</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_19_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Eftersom din Krigarenhet har förbrukat alla sina [ICON_Movement] Förflyttningspoäng är den klar med sina åtgärder för den här omgången.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Både produktions- och forskningsuppgiften pågår fortfarande så det finns inga andra beslut att fatta.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_19b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på knappen ”Nästa omgång” igen för att fortsätta.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_9_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VÄLJ KRIGARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_9_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på Krigar-enheten för att välja den.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_2_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>GRUNDA EN STAD</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_2_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på knappen ”Grunda stad” för att instruera Nybyggaren att grunda en ny stad på den här platsen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_3_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VISA PRODUKTION</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_3_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Öppna den här stadens Produktionsväljare genom att klicka på knappen ”Ändra produktion”.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_4a_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>PRODUKTIONSVÄLJAREN</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_4a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det här är stadens Produktionsväljare. Här kan du konstruera byggnader, skapa underverk, och träna både militära och civila enheter.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_4b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Select the Warrior button to start training a Warrior unit in your city.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_5a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>”Civilization” är ett omgångsbaserat spel där beslut fattas och åtgärder utförs under en spelomgång, på samma sätt som när man spelar ett brädspel tillsammans med kamrater. När alla de andra spelarna har gjort sina drag kan en ny spelomgång börja.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_5b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Att bygga saker i staden tar tid. Hur många omgångar som kommer behövas visas intill varje sak i menyn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Det här värdet baseras på sakens [ICON_Production] Produktionskostnad i förhållande till hur stor avkastning av [ICON_Production] Produktion staden har. Ju högre avkastning, desto färre omgångar behövs för att bygga saken.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_5_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>AVSLUTA OMGÅNG</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_5_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på knappen ”Nästa omgång” för att avsluta din spelomgång.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_7a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The Research Panel displays what technology your civilization is currently working toward. It is empty because you have not yet chosen a technology to research.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_7_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VÄLJ FORSKNING</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_7_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Välj vetenskapen Gruvdrift från menyn för att börja forska fram den.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_10_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FLYTTA KRIGARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_10_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Militära enheter kan attackera fiende-enheter genom att de flyttas in i fiendens ruta. Högerklicka på barbaren för att attackera den. Försök att göra det nu.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_27_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>BYGG MONUMENT</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_27_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>I tillägg till att träna enheter kan din stad också fokusera sin produktion på att konstruera byggnader som till exempel ett Monument.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Försök bygga ett nu genom att välja det i stadens Produktionskö.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_21' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>With Barbarians in our midst, I think our people would be more comfortable if our Warriors were closer to the city. Order them to return and defend.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_28a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Enheter kan beordras att flytta längre distanser genom att man ger dem en fleromgångsorder. Detta gör att man slipper ge dem nya förflyttningsinstruktioner varje omgång för att nå destinationen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_28_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FLYTTA KRIGARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_28_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Försök att beordra krigaren att återvända till staden genom att klicka på knappen ”Flytta till”, och sen klicka på staden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_29_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>When using a multi-move order, a path will display on the map indicating the path the unit will take, along with indicators of the number of turns until it reaches the destination.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_22' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, our Scouts are eager to explore the surrounding lands and uncover new areas of the continent. Send them forth!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_23' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det finns inga fler ärenden som måste hanteras för närvarande, ers nåd.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_24' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our brightest minds have discovered new and ingenious ways to extract precious stones and metals from the earth. There is an abundance of valuable Stone nearby, it would be wise to send our Builders to construct a Quarry there.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_30_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Resurser av olika slag är utspridda över kartan. Det finns tre typer av resurser::[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Lyxresurser: Dessa bidrar till dina invånares belåtenhet och lycka.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Strategiska resurser: Nödvändiga för att skapa vissa mycket kraftfulla militära enheter.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Bonusresurser: Ger ytterligare avkastning av [ICON_Food] Mat , [ICON_Production] Produktion, eller [ICON_Gold] Guld.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_31a_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>BYGG STENBROTT</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_31a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Den här Stenen är en Bonusresurs. Den ger ytterligare +1 [ICON_Production]Produktion i staden.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Om du bygger förbättringen Stenbrott här kommer det öka avkastningen till +2 [ICON_Production]Produktion.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_31b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Flytta Byggar-enheten till Stenresursen, och få dem att konstruera ett Stenbrott där.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_32_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Stenbrottsförbättringar ökar [ICON_Production]Produktionen i staden de hör till. Högre Produktion gör att enheter och byggnader kan konstrueras fortare. Enkelt uttryckt gör högre Produktion att det krävs färre omgångar för att bygga något i staden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_26' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Våra invånare känner sig lättare över Krigarnas återkomst till staden. Får jag föreslå att de antar en mer defensiv position för tillfället? De kommer vara på sin vakt mot hotet från barbarerna.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_27' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Goda nyheter! Våra hantverkare har slutfört konstruktionen av Monumentet i vår stad! Det är en symbol för vår civilisations bedrifter och uthållighet, och inspirerar vårt folk att våga sig längre in i markerna bortanför gränsen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_28' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, we should expand our realm. We have adventurous families ready to strike out and claim new lands for the glory of our people. If we do not expand our borders, then in time we will find ourselves surrounded by our enemies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_29' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Settlers will take some time to complete their training. Our Scout should continue exploring undiscovered lands. I would advise we keep our Warriors in the [ICON_Capital] Capital to defend it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_30' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The Settlers are ready to embark on their journey to found a new city and expand our civilization. The lands beyond are dangerous, and it would be wise to insure their protection by sending them with a military escort.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_31' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our Settlers should be safe on their journey under the protection of our Warriors. But we will be without protection in the [ICON_Capital] Capital once they leave. I suggest we begin training a Slinger unit immediately to defend the city.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_32' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Well done, Your Majesty. Our great minds have already begun work on new ways to store and preserve our food.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_33' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>May the triumphs of our great civilization know no bounds! Our second great city awaits your direction. With your wise leadership it too shall grow and thrive.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_34' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Like our [ICON_Capital] Capital, this city can produce buildings and units, increase its population, and expand its borders. More cities means more to manage, but I have great faith in Your Majesty.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_36' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty has shown wisdom and understanding in the fundamentals of ruling a civilization. I shall be available to assist you at any point should you wish, but for now I take my leave.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_37' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our farmers are very skilled at providing [ICON_Food] Food for our people, but we need to find better ways to store it. I suggest we direct the efforts of our scientists to solving this problem.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_39' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our dedication to developing a consistent written language has allowed us to record our knowledge for future use. If we were to provide a common location in our city for our scientists to share this information I'm sure their pursuits would be much more efficient.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_40' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Excellent! Construction on a Campus has begun. Our scientists look forward to its completion.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_41' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The Campus is complete and we have already begun to see its benefits. Construction of a Library would be ideal at such a location, should your highness agree to it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_42' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It seems we are not the only people competing for control of these lands. I suggest we proceed with caution.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_43' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Highness we are at war. Security of the realm is of greatest importance. We must begin mobilizing an army immediately.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_44' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Uniting your governance with a strict code of laws can be most beneficial to us. I think it is time to enact a set of policies to strengthen our progress toward a more refined civilization.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_45' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Strict discipline in our military ranks would give us an edge against the unorganized Barbarian horde. More structured Urban Planning will make our cities more organized and efficient. I suggest we enact these policies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_46' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Nurturing our populace is important, but we must also protect them. There are barbaric tribes near us who want nothing more than to pillage and plunder what is ours.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_47' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We continue to make progress on training a team of Builders, and research is continuing as planned. [NEWLINE] Our Warriors are very close to the Tribal Village and should arrive soon.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_48' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our people have looked to the heavens, and begun to wonder if our fortunes may be guided by the hands of a greater power. Who are these great gods, and what blessings might they bestow on us?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_49' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In a life dedicated to searching for guidance in the mysteries of the universe, one has had an epiphany that will guide our faithful for millennia to come. Let the teachings of this Great Prophet spread people of all cultures across the face of the earth. By proliferating our Religion, we may be victorious over our rivals.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_50' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Congratulations, My Liege! Your leadership has inspired our people to greatness, and now one among them has attained true genius. Their contribution will reverberate throughout history.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_51' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, we must reach out to our neighbors in trade. Through them, we stand to boost our economy, and gain new insights into the mysteries of the world.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_52' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>My Liege, we have made contact with some outsiders. These people are more advanced than the Tribal Villagers that have aided us in the past. Should we extend a hand in friendship, or seek to conquer them?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_53' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Caution, your majesty. This city is hostile to us and its people will surely fight to the bitter end to keep it out of our hands. We must be well prepared</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_33_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VÄLJ FORSKNING</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_332_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VÄLJ FORSKNING</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_332_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på knappen ”Välj Forskning” för att visa Forskningsväljaren.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_331_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>CHANGE RESEARCH</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_33_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Välj vetenskapen Krukmakeri från Forskningsmenyn.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_34_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>NOTIFICATIONS</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_34_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>If there are units that have not moved this turn and are awaiting orders, you can address them by clicking the Unit Needs Orders notification. Click the notification now to be taken to your Scout unit so you may issue new orders.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_35_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>MOVE SCOUT</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_35_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Fortsätt att utforska världen med din Spejarenhet.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_36a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>När en militär enhet inte befinner sig i förflyttning är det ofta en god idé att befästa enheten. När enheten beordras att befästa sin position, kommer den använda upp till 2 omgångar för att förstärka sin position. Detta kommer ge den högre [ICON_Strength] Stridsstyrka om den blir attackerad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_36_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>BEFÄST KRIGAREN</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_36_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Försök att beordra Krigaren att göra så genom att klicka på knappen ”Befäst”.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_37_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FORTIFY BONUS</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_37_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Den här enheten kommer nu ha en fördel när den försvarar sig i strid. Om enheten flyttas kommer den dock förlora sin befästa status, och måste beordras befästa sig igen för att få bonusen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_38_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>BUILDER WORKFORCE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_38a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Din Byggare har fortfarande en del av sin arbetsstyrka kvar.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Du kan antingen använda den för att bygga en Gruva på rutan med Kullen (+[ICON_Production] Produktion), eller en Bondgård på Slätt-rutan (+[ICON_Food] Mat).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Detta kan kräva mer än en spelomgång – en för att flyttta enheten, och ytterligare en för att bygga förbättringen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_38b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Kom ihåg: Byggare kan bara konstruera förbättringar innanför din stads gränser.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Genom att generera [ICON_Culture] Kultur kommer din stads gränser expandera, och ge dig tillgång till fler resurser.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_39_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>UTFORSKNING</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_39_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Fortsätt gärna utforska kartan med din Spejar-enhet. Avsluta din spelomgång när du är klar med att ge order till både Byggaren och Spejaren.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_40_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your city has finished production on the Monument building. All buildings contribute to a city’s development in specific ways. The Monument will increase the [ICON_Culture] Culture generated by the city, which extends the city’s influence over additional hexes.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_41_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>TRAIN SETTLERS</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_41_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Begin training a Settler unit.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_41b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Open the Production Chooser and begin training a Settler unit. Remember, the Production Chooser can either be accessed from the city's Information Panel or from the Choose Production reminder in the Notification Panel on the right side of the game view.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_42_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Units like Settlers and Builders are non-combat, civilian units and thus cannot defend themselves. This leaves them highly vulnerable to be captured or killed by enemy units. However, your military units can act as protection for the civilian unit if they occupy the same hex.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_43a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>An easy way to move the two units together is by linking them together until they reach their destination.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_43_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>ESCORT SETTLER</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_43_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Select either the Settler or the Warrior and click the Escort button in the unit panel.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_44_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>MOVE FORMATION</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_44_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Begin moving the units southeast toward the indicated map marker. If you have not yet revealed that part of the map it might make your journey easier if you sent your Scout there as well.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_45a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In a game of Civilization, once a player loses all of their cities, the game is over. It is very important that you protect your cities, especially your [ICON_Capital] Capital, from any foreign threat.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_45_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>TRAIN SLINGERS</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_45_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Add a Slinger unit to the city's Production Queue and end your turn when you are finished.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_46_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>As is often the case in history, technological discoveries inspire new technologies, building upon knowledge gained in the past. In a game of Civilization, this is simulated by the Technology Tree. Click the open Technology Tree button in the Research Panel to view it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_46a_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Öppna Vetenskapsträdet</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_46a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka för att öppna Vetenskapsträdet</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_47_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The Technology Tree displays all of the researchable technologies available in a game of Civilization, from the Ancient era all the way to the Information era and beyond.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_48_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The gold colored nodes represent technologies that you have already finished researching. You have just finished researching Pottery, so it has been marked as complete.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_49_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The dark grey nodes represent technologies that are available to begin researching, but are not complete.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_50_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Light grey nodes represent technologies that are not yet available to begin researching. These technologies need to first be unlocked by researching one or more prerequisite technologies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_51a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Since we have already researched Pottery, we are now able to begin research on the Writing technology.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_51_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VÄLJ FORSKNING</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_51_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Start research on Writing by clicking on the Writing node in the Technology Tree.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_52_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Notice the Writing technology node status has changed, indicating that it is currently being researched. The number of turns required to finish research on a technology is indicated in the upper right corner of the node.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_53A_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The symbols displayed inside the technology node represent new units, buildings, wonders and abilities that are unlocked by the technology once it is completed.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_53B_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>For example, once you have finished researching the Writing technology, you will be able to construct the Campus district as well as the Library building in all of your cities. The Campus and Library allow you to increase the amount of [ICON_Science] Science you generate each turn, allowing you to research technologies faster! </Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_54_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Since you're done designating new research, we can close the Technology Tree by clicking the X button in the upper right corner.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_54a_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Close Tree</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_54a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click to close the Technology Tree</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_55_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Continue moving your Settler unit to the indicated location.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_56_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In choosing a location to settle a new city, it is important to look at the fertility of the surrounding land. Proximity to sources of [ICON_Food] Food, resources, and fresh water are all very important. For this tutorial we have already found an ideal location for you.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_57_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>When your Settler unit is able, click the Found City button to create a new city here. This may require moving on to the next turn if your Settler is out of [ICON_Movement] Movement points.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_58_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>To win a game of Civilization, as a player you need to defeat all other civilizations in the world. There are multiple ways to achieve this. You can conquer their cities militarily, bringing them into your civilization. You can also win technologically, or through cultural or religious dominance.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_59_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>On the path to victory, there are fundamental strategies to assist you in building your civilization.[NEWLINE]---[NEWLINE]For this tutorial, we have provided four goals for you to achieve. Complete all four and you can complete the tutorial. However, in order to WIN the tutorial, you need to complete the fifth goal.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_61_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Congratulations![NEWLINE]---[NEWLINE]You have completed the fundamentals of growing and maintaining a civilization that will stand the test of time. You can finish the tutorial, or you can keep playing and win this game by eliminating the rival civ.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_63_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In this tutorial you are playing on a small map with a single rival civilization. A standard game of Civilization presents a larger map of the world, with several rival civilizations, all competing to win. The task is larger, but the goals remain the same.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_62_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>To win this game, you must conquer all the rival civilization’s city(s) with your military.[NEWLINE]---[NEWLINE]Good luck!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_76_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Open the Production Chooser of your first city by clicking the production button on the City Banner.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_77_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In Civilization VI, there are many types of districts that can be built in your cities, each with a specific purpose.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_78_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>By completing research on Writing, you are now able to construct a Campus district in your city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Campus district is dedicated to increasing the amount of [ICON_Science] Science generated by the city that contains it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_79_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Many districts in the game also get a bonus depending on where they are placed within the city. The Campus gets a bonus when built next to Mountains or Jungles.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_80_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>BUILD CAMPUS</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_80_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click the Campus button in the Production Chooser to start building one in this city.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_81_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>When placing a district, the map changes slightly to indicate ideal locations in which to build it. </Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_82_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This plot has Mountains on two of its edges, each providing +1 [ICON_Science] Science per turn. Placing the Campus here would be ideal.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_83_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click this hex to begin building a Campus here.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_84_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Since you have finished the Writing technology, you now must choose what to research next. If you would like a suggestion, Animal Husbandry and Bronze Working are both good choices.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_85_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Animal Husbandry will allow you to build the Pasture and Camp improvements in your cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Bronze Working will help you militarily by unlocking the Encampment district, as well as allow you to train Spearmen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_86_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Some buildings can only be constructed in districts. The Library is a building exclusive to the Campus district. Since we have completed construction on the Campus, we are now able to build a Library on it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_87_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>BUILD LIBRARY</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_87_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click the Choose Production button in the lower right to begin building a Library.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_88_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Congratulations!![NEWLINE]You have won your first game of Civilization.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You are now ready to take on much larger challenges and objectives, explore new worlds, meet new civilizations for the first time, and achieve victory on your terms.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_89_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>When engaged in a war with another civilization, it is best to have a sufficient number of combat units, both to defend your cities as well as fight abroad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_90_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Sometimes it is necessary to suspend production on a building or district in order to train units to fight the war. To do this, simply change the current production task of the city to the combat unit you wish to create.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_91_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>When you are satisfied with the size of your military, you can resume production on what was being built previously without losing the progress you made on it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_92_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Engaging in diplomatic relations with other civilizations can be very lucrative. Of course, relations can also go sour. How you interact with other leaders is your choice. Just remember, in the path to victory, you cannot always be everyone’s friend.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_93a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Genom att samla [ICON_Culture] Kultur har du just låst upp Lagsamling, you have just unlocked Code of Laws, som innehåller ditt första statsskick: Hövdingadöme.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_93b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>STATSSKICK</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_93b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>To access it, click the Government button.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_94_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det finns många typer av statsskick i Civilization VI. I tillägg till olika andra fördelar har varje statsskick ett antal platser där du kan anta politiska inriktningar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_95a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det första statsskicket som har blivit tillgängligt är Hövdingadöme. Det har 2 tillgängliga politikplatser. Den första platsen är för Militär politik, den andra är för Ekonomisk politik.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_95b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>REGERINGSPOLITIK</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_95b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på knappen ”Ändra Politik”</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_96_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>För att lägga in en politisk inriktning, klicka och dra politikkortet från högra delen till rätt politikplats till vänster.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Pröva det nu genom att lägga till kortet Disciplin till platsen för Militär politik, och sedan kortet Stadsplanering till platsen för Ekonomisk politik. Klicka på knappen ”Bekräfta Politik” när du är klar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_97_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>By enacting these policies, your military units will now get a +5 [ICON_Strength] Combat Strength bonus when fighting against Barbarians. Also, your cities receive +1 [ICON_Production] Production per turn, allowing them to train units and construct buildings faster than before.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_98_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Much in the same way you research new technologies by generating [ICON_Science] Science in your cities, you unlock civics by generating [ICON_Culture] Culture.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You have already unlocked the Code of Laws civic which enabled you to establish your first government.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_99a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Now you need to select a new civic to advance toward.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_99b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>CIVICS TREE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_99b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Open the Civics Tree by clicking the Civics Tree button in the upper left corner of the screen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_100_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Similar to the Technology Tree, the Civics Tree has different choices and paths as you progress through the game.[NEWLINE]For this tutorial, click the Craftsmanship civic to start advancing next.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_100b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>CHOOSE CIVIC</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_100b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Select the Craftsmanship civic</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_100c_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Close Tree</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_100c_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click to close the Civics Tree</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_101_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på ”Nästa omgång” för att fortsätta.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_102_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>TRÄNA BYGGARE</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_102_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på ”Byggare” för att börja utbilda en Byggarenhet.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_103_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Städerna är hörnpelaren i alla stora civilisationer. En stads storlek representeras av dess [ICON_Citizen]Befolkning, som visas till vänster om namnplattan.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_103_OTHER_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A Slinger unit has finished training in your capital. Slingers are ranged class units, allowing them to attack from distance without engaging in melee combat. This keeps them from taking reciprocal damage during the attack.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_104_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Varje stad lägger också beslag på den omgivande marken, så att den blir din. Vidden av ditt landområde indikeras av den färglagda gränsen runt staden. Vilka marktyper som hamnar innanför gränsen kommer ha en stor betydelse för dina städers potentiella styrka.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_104_OTHER_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Ranged units also tend to have lower defense strength than their melee fighting counterparts, so it is best to keep them close to friendly units of other types for protection.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_105_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Du måste bestämma hur varje stad i din civilisation ska växa och expandera med tiden, hur du ska förbättra marken som står under din kontroll, och skapa nya byggnader och distrikt innanför dina gränser.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_105_OTHER_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>As you progress through the game and research new technologies, you will unlock better, stronger, and more advanced units. Building a strong and diverse fighting force is essential in competing against other civilizations, and preserving the safety of your people.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_WRITING_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have just completed research on Writing.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_POTTERY_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>I tillägg till [ICON_Food] Mat behöver ditt folk också [ICON_Amenities] Bekvämligheter i sina städer. En källa till [ICON_Amenities] Bekvämlighet är Lyxresurser, som till exempel den här [ICON_Resource_Coffee] Kaffe-resursen nära din [ICON_Capital] Huvudstad. Nu när forskningen av Krukmakeriet är klar vore det en god idé att forska fram Konstbevattning härnäst, för att det möjligt för dina Byggare att förbättra lyxresurser som just detta [ICON_Resource_Coffee] Kaffe. Detta kommer förse vår stad med [ICON_Amenities] Bekvämlighet, och öka dess lycka.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_GOAL_6_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have completed the goal of improving a tile within range of the second city!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_GOAL_8_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have completed the goal of exploring another tribal village!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_GOAL_9_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have completed the goal of growing a city to a population of six!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_GOAL_10_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have completed the goal of building five improvements!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_GOAL_14_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have completed the goal of constructing Walls in your [ICON_Capital] Capital city!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_GOAL_15_COMPLETE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have completed the goal of constructing a Barracks!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_106_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Varje stad genererar olika typer av avkastning vid början av varje ny omgång. Denna avkastning kommer från de rutor som staden kontrollerar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_107_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Varje ruta innanför dina stadsgränser kan ge ett antal olika avkastningar som hjälper dig föra din civilisation framåt. [ICON_Food] Mat och [ICON_Production] Produktion är två typer av avkastning.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] [ICON_Food] Mat är bränslet för din stads tillväxt, så att din [ICON_Citizen] Befolkning ökar. Ju mer [ICON_Food] Mat, desto snabbare tillväxt.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]  [ICON_Production] Produktion används för att bygga nya föremål, som till exempel militära enheter och stadsförbättringar. Ju mer [ICON_Production] Produktion din stad har, desto fortare kan du bygga saker.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_108_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Dock måste en ruta brukas av din [ICON_Citizen] Befolkning för att du ska kunna få avkastningen från den rutan.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Varje [ICON_Citizen]Invånare kan bruka 1 ruta innanför dina gränser.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_109_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Att öka stadens [ICON_Citizen]Befolkning är väldigt viktigt för att kunna dra nytta av all avkastning från den omgivande marken.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_110_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It is now up to you to decide what you would like to produce in this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Suggestions:[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]- Train a Builder to improve more of the surrounding lands within your borders.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]- Train a combat unit to expand the size and strength of your military.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-Build a Granary to provide additional [ICON_Food] Food for your city as well as more [ICON_Housing] Housing for your [ICON_Citizen] Population.</Text>		</Replace>		<!---->		<!--TUTORIAL GOALS TEXT-->		<!---->		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_GENERAL_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Mål:</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_GENERAL_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Att SLUTFÖRA handledningen:</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_GENERAL_3' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Att VINNA handledningen:</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>UTFORSKA: Utforska oupptäckta områden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_TOOLTIP_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Använd din spejare för att hitta och utforska alla Stambyar i området.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FÖRSVAR: Flytta Krigaren tillbaka till staden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_TOOLTIP_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Flytta tillbaka Krigaren till staden som försvar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_3' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FÖRSVAR: Behåll Krigaren i staden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_TOOLTIP_3' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Håll Krigaren i staden för att försvara den.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_4' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>TRÄNA NYBYGGARE: Fullborda träningen av en Nybyggarenhet.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_TOOLTIP_4' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Fullborda träningen av en Nybyggarenhet för att expandera din civilisation.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_5' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>GRUNDA EN NY STAD: Eskortera Nybyggaren till den bestämda platsen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_TOOLTIP_5' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Eskortera Nybyggaren med din Krigare till den bestämda platsen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_6' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>UTVECKLA: Använd Byggaren för att förbättra marken kring den nya staden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_TOOLTIP_6' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Använd en Byggare för att förbättra marken kring den nya staden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_7' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VETENSKAP: Konstruera ett Campus i din huvudstad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_TOOLTIP_7' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Fullborda konstruktionen av ett Campus i din huvudstad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_8' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Hitta och utforska en annan Stamby.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_9' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Uppnå en Befolkning på 6 i någon av dina städer.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_10' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>UTNYTTJA: Bygg 5 förbättringar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_11' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>UTPLÅNA: Eliminera hotet från barbarerna i ditt område, och förstör barbarlägret.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_12' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Eliminera den andra civilisationen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_13' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>BYGG FÖRBÄTTRING: Använd din Byggarenhet för att konstruera en tredje förbättring i din stad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_14' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Bygg Antika murar i din huvudstad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_15' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Bygg ett Militärförläggningsdistrikt och uppgradera det med en Kasern.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_16' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Träna fem Militära enheter, inklusive minst en Bågskytt eller Murbräcka. [EJ IMPLEMENTERAT].</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_TUTORIAL_GOAL_17' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>FÖR ATT VINNA: Eliminera den andra civilisationen genom att erövra deras huvudstad.</Text>		</Replace>		<!---->		<!--CITY PANEL BUILT-IN ADVISOR MESSAGES-->		<!---->		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_HOUSING_INTRO' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>TO GAIN HOUSING:</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_AMENITY_INTRO' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>TO GAIN AMENITIES:</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_CONSTRUCT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Construct Buildings: {1_Buildings}</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_ZONE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add Districts: {1_Districts}</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_BUILD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Place Improvements: {1_Improvements}</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_IMPROVE_LUXURIES' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Improve Luxury resources.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_RESEARCH' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Research Technology: {1_Techs}</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_CITYPANEL_CULTUREVATE' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Unlock Civics: {1_Civics}</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_53_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The symbols displayed inside the technology node represent new units, buildings, wonders, and abilities that are unlocked by the technology once it is completed. For example, once you have finished researching the Pottery technology, you will be able to construct the Granary building in all of your cities. Your Builders will also gain the ability to harvest Wheat resources near your city. While harvesting a Wheat resource gives you a large amount of [ICON_Food] Food, that resource is removed from the map. In most cases, it is better to nurture a Wheat resource by building a Farm improvement on it instead.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_167_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Ditt folks tekniska utveckling uppnås genom forskning.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Genom att utveckla nya vetenskaper kommer du att låsa upp nya sätt att utnyttja marken, nya militära enheter, nya förbättringar av städerna, och mycket mer.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_111_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Precis som byggandet av nya enheter får ”bränsle” från [ICON_Production] Produktion, så får utvecklingen av nya vetenskaper bränsle från [ICON_Science] Vetenskap.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_112_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Varje stad i ditt rike genererar en liten mängd [ICON_Science] Vetenskap per omgång. Hur snabbt dina forskningsprojekt fullbordas beror på hur mycket [ICON_Science] Vetenskap som genereras av dina städer. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Ju mer [ICON_Science] Vetenskap du genererar, desto fortare kan du utveckla nya vetenskaper.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_SELECT_IRRIGATION' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Välj Konstbevattning från Forskningsväljarpanelen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_6_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>VÄLJ FORSKNING</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_6_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på knappen ”Välj Forskning” för att visa Forskningspanelen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_113_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>(För handledningens skull så har vi snabbat på tillverkningen av den här enheten. Normalt skulle tillverkningen ha behövt ytterligare ett antal omgångar för att bli klar.)</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_12_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click the Choose Production notification to open the city’s Production Menu.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_15_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Klicka på Krigar-enheten för att välja den.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_114_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Alla Stambyar ger en belöning när de utforskas av en spelare. Den här Stambyn har gett dig en ny Spejarenhet, som har dykt upp i din stad.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_115_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Continue exploring the world with your Scout. End turn when its action is complete.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_116_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Din civilisation kommer alltid forska fram nya vetenskaper. Eftersom du just blivit klar med Gruvdrift måste du nu välja vad du vill forska fram härnäst, innan du kan fortsätta till nästa spelomgång.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_117_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Forskningen av vetenskapen Krukmakeri har börjat. Avsluta din spelomgång efter att du har flyttat din Spejare.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_118_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>To win a game of Civilization, you need to defeat all other civilizations in the world. There are multiple ways to achieve this. Most games will also end in the year 2050 or after a set number of turns. If no player has achieved these Victories by then, score will determine the winner. Score is calculated as a general measure of each player’s achievements in all fields of endeavor.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_119_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The status of each Victory’s conditions are tracked on the World Rankings panel. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Open it now.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_119a_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>World Rankings</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_119a_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click to open the World Rankings panel</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_120_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The Overall tab gives you an overview of all types of Victory and your ranking against other players</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_121_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The other tabs give you more specific detail about each set of rankings. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Close the panel when you are ready to proceed.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_122_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The rest of this tutorial will help you to achieve your first Domination Victory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The goal of a Domination Victory is for your civilization to be the last to occupy its own [ICON_Capital] Capital city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]For this tutorial, that means you will have to use your military to capture the [ICON_Capital] Capital city of your rival, while preventing them from taking yours.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]How you ultimately achieve this will be up to you. However, we have provided three optional objectives that, if completed, will greatly assist you in achieving this.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_123_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>If you are unsure about something, or are looking for more information about anything you’ve seen in this tutorial, there’s a good chance you’ll find it in the Civilopedia.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_64_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Districts are specific areas of your city dedicated to providing a specific yield. Buildings can be constructed in districts to increase that yield while also providing other benefits for your city.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_65_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>For example, you have unlocked the {DISTRICT_TYPE} district which is dedicated to providing {YIELD_TYPE} to your civilization. Constructing a {DISTRICT_BUILDING} building in this district increases the {YIELD_TYPE} yield for your civilization.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_66_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>To zone a district, select it in your city’s production menu as you would a building or a unit. Some districts have rules of where they can be placed, but even more important is that districts can have an even greater benefit if placed in an optimal location.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_67_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>When you are ready to zone a district, the game will assist you in choosing the best location. Sometimes you might not have a valid spot in your city to place a new district right away. The location may have to be cleared of obstructions, or all of your existing city plots may already have improvements.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_68_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Expanding the size of your city is one way to gain more locations for districts, as well as improvements.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_ADVISOR_LINE_5' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your Majesty, if I may… Although our scientists would be willing to explore other topics of research, I feel it is best to not distract them until they have completed their current project unless absolutely necessary.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_69_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Any research progress on a technology is not lost, so there are cases where changing your research focus is strategically valid. However, it is always better to have a completed technology rather than many incomplete ones.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_73_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>In Civilization VI, you can get Eureka Moments that boost your technology research through in game achievements. This Eureka Moment was gained by discovering a natural wonder. Other achievements could be winning a battle with a specific unit or constructing a building. Achieving these greatly accelerates your technological progress.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_127_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Scouts are ideal for investigating Tribal Villages because they receive experience from it.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_72_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Any production progress on an item in the queue is not lost, so there are cases where changing your city’s production focus is strategically valid. However, it is often best to finish what you have started before starting something new.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_74_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Du noterade kanske att din Byggar-enhet försvann efter att den använde sin sista byggnation. Detta skedde eftersom sista delen av dess arbetsstyrka förbrukades. Du kommer behöva utbilda fler Byggare under spelets gång för att förbättra markerna runt dina städer.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_75_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Scouts, unlike other military units, gain experience from exploring Tribal Villages. They can also gain experience from discovering natural wonders in the world. </Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_128_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You may have noticed that your cities have been generating a small amount of [ICON_Faith] Faith each turn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Faith] Faith is earned over time by certain buildings, districts, and policies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_129_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Now that you’ve earned enough [ICON_Faith] Faith, you are able to take the first step towards founding a Religion by forming a Pantheon, which will provide you with a choice of strategic benefits.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_129b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Choose Pantheon</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_129b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click the Religion button to open the Religion screen and choose a Pantheon.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_129c' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are many Pantheons to choose from with different gameplay effects. Once one is chosen by a player, it is removed from the list of available Pantheons and is exclusive to that player’s religion for the duration of the game. Choose wisely!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_129d' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Choose a Pantheon, then click the 'Found this Pantheon' button when you are done.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_130_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Well done! The next step is to attract a Great Prophet, who will be able to found a Religion. But first, you will need to build a Holy Site district, or enact an appropriate government policy, both of which will earn you Great Prophet Points.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_131_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are a limited number of opportunities to found a Religion. Doing so is optional, but keep in mind that if you do not, you may not have an effective counter against a player who is seeking a Religious Victory by converting your [ICON_Citizen] Citizens.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_131b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Close Religion</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_132_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your [ICON_GreatProphet] Great Prophet has founded a new Religion, and you must customize it by selecting a name, symbol, and selecting two additional religious beliefs that will complement the Pantheon belief you selected previously.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_133_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your new Religion can spread between cities, converting its [ICON_Citizen] Citizens into followers. It is possible for a city to have a mix of several Religions. The Religion with the majority of followers in a city will be the one that imparts its bonuses.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_134_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>While Religion will slowly spread from city to city organically, you can cause sudden shifts by training Missionary and Apostle units and sending them out to spread your people’s Religion. These units can be obtained by spending [ICON_Faith] Faith to buy them in the Purchase tab of a city’s Production Menu.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_135_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Aggressively spreading your Religion is essential if you are targeting a Religious Victory. Even if you are not, it is wise to keep track of how Religion is spreading around the world. Counter it where possible to mitigate the chances of another player claiming Victory this way.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_136_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have gained the opportunity to claim a [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person for your civilization. [ICON_GreatPerson] Great People provide significant benefits to your civilization based on their field. There are many types of [ICON_GreatPerson] Great People, including artists, engineers, and military leaders.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_136b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Great People</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_136b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Open the [ICON_GreatPerson] Great People panel to claim your [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_137_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This is the [ICON_GreatPerson] Great People panel. It shows all the [ICON_GreatPerson] Great People that are currently available for civilizations to claim, their benefits, and their costs.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_138_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Each [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person has one or more opportunities to activate a special bonus. They will appear as a unit in one of your cities and you must Activate their bonus at a special location on the map. Once they have used all their bonuses, the [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person will disappear.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_139_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person is earned by saving up enough [ICON_GreatPerson] Great People Points of its type, then spending them to recruit the [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person to your civilization. These points come primarily from districts and buildings, but can also come from policies and other effects. If you are in a rush, you can spend [ICON_Gold] Gold or [ICON_Faith] Faith to instantly earn the [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person you want.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_140_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You can choose to pass on a [ICON_GreatPerson] Great Person that you don’t want. If you do this, then other players will have the opportunity to claim them, and your choice to pass is not reversible. However, your [ICON_GreatPerson] Great People Points will be saved for a future opportunity.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_141_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You’ve just completed a Trader unit. Traders travel between two cities and generate income for their city of origin. </Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_142_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your civilization can establish a limited number of [ICON_TradeRoute] Trade Routes. You can expand this capacity with Commercial Hub or Harbor districts.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_142b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Assign Trade Route</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_142b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click the 'Assign Trade Route' unit action.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_143_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are no other cities to trade with right now. Continue to explore the map, or build a Settler and found a new city of your own.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_144_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This is the Trade Panel, showing the cities that you can trade with currently. Traders have a limited range, but visiting nearby cities will establish a Trading Post there, allowing them to be used as a bridge to farther destinations.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_145_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Depending on the buildings and districts within a foreign destination, you stand to earn yields of [ICON_Science] Science, [ICON_Faith] Faith, [ICON_Culture] Culture, or [ICON_Gold] Gold each turn for a set number of turns. For domestic destinations, you can earn [ICON_Food] Food and [ICON_Production] Production.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_145b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Select the destination of your choice from the list of available cities.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_145c_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click 'Begin Route' to send this Trader on its way to the destination.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_146_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This Trader will now travel to the destination and back, generating the relevant yields each turn. Once it has returned, you can choose a new route.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_147_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The Trader will also build a Road between the cities as it goes. Units travelling a road generally suffer no terrain [ICON_Movement] Movement penalties.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_148_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have discovered a nearby city-state. These are mini-civilizations that are similar in some ways to another player, but they can only ever have a single city and cannot win the game. By working with your city-state neighbors, you can build lucrative relationships and even gain their support in war.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_149_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You can also choose to forcefully assimilate their cities into your empire or raze them to the ground – but they are far more formidable than Barbarians to defeat, and you risk alienating their other allies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_150_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click the city-state button or click the city-state to open the city state panel.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_151_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This is the city-state panel. You can earn Envoys and dispatch them to a city-state. Doing this can earn you progressively better buffs to [ICON_Science] Science, [ICON_Culture] Culture, [ICON_Production] Production, [ICON_Gold] Gold, or [ICON_Faith] Faith. Click the name of a city-state in the list.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_152_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>These are the Quests you can complete for this city-state. This is one way to earn Envoys and improve your friendship with it. You can also earn Envoys by completing certain items in the Civics Tree, and over time through governments and policies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_153_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your unit is getting close to an enemy city. Attacking cities is usually a difficult and potentially costly undertaking that requires a mix of unit types and a tactical approach.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_154_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The city’s defense rating and health bar is shown on its Name Plate. This city has Walls. It will be able to launch a ranged attack from 2 hexes away, and will be highly resistant to melee units.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_155_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Certain siege units can improve your chances. Catapults can attack from range and do significant damage to Walls, while the Battering Ram or Siege Tower allows melee units to attack Walls or bypass them, respectively.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_156_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You have met the leader of another civilization. In Civilization VI, there will typically be several other civilizations sharing the world map with you. These are controlled by the game AI, and have all the same abilities – and ambitions – that you do.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_157_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>As you play, you will need to consider how to deal with your neighbors and watch them carefully to improve your understanding of their strategy.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_158_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Leaders of civilizations you have met in the game will appear here. The leader icon on the far right represents your civilization. All other leaders will be listed to next to yours.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_158b_HEAD' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Leader Diplomacy</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_158b_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Click the other civilization leader's icon to access the Diplomacy view.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_159_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>When you contact another leader, you can take a variety of actions, like exchanging goods, negotiating political treaties, making demands, or declaring war.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_160_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You can send a Delegation to improve your ties and expose more information about their [ICON_Capital] Capital city. </Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_161_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Denouncing a rival notifies all other civilizations that you have a bone to pick. This paves the way to war. If you do not make your feelings known, the war you declare will be a Surprise War, inflicting a lasting “Warmonger” reputation on you that may color future dealings with other leaders.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_162_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>You can also negotiate deals with a leader. This can include trading commodities or political deals like Open Borders or Joint War. Alternatively, you can demand that they deal with you. This will sour your relationship, but they may acquiesce if they are weak or wish to avoid war.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_163_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>What you know about this leader is summarized here. Be mindful of their Agendas. If you act in opposition to their Agendas, your relationship with them may sour and potentially lead to conflict.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_164_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Improving your Access Level to this civilization will expose more detailed information about them, and you’ll be notified when they take certain actions. It's a good idea to improve this as much as possible with the leaders you encounter, or you will be in the dark as to their strategy.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_165_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>This section explains what the leader thinks about you, and why. If you wish to improve (or sour) your relationship, you’ll find some suggestions here. It may not be possible to avoid doing something that annoys them from time to time, so it can be useful to know how to balance the books.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_166_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Diplomacy will become increasingly important as you progress through history. Who your neighbors are and want they want will have a lasting impact on the development of your civilization – and will almost certainly present obstacles in your path to victory.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_168_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>En stadstat är en liten civilisation som inte kan vinna spelet. Att etablera goda diplomatiska relationer med dem kan vara väldigt lönsamt. Detta görs genom att skicka Sändebud till stadsstaten.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='LOC_META_169_BODY' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Trader units can be trained in one of your cities. In addition to providing additional [ICON_Gold] Gold and other benefits to your civilization, [ICON_TradeRoute] Trade Routes are essential for building roads between cities.</Text>		</Replace>		<!---->		<!--ROCCO LINES-->		<!---->				<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_1ALT_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Välkommen, Kleopatra. Vårt folks öde ligger i dina händer. Ett stort ansvar har lagts på dina axlar. Kanske jag kan vara till hjälp?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_1ALT_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Välkommen, Gilgamesh. Vårt folks öde ligger i dina händer. Ett stort ansvar har lagts på dina axlar. Kanske jag kan vara till hjälp?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_2_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Alltför länge har vi strövat runt i världen utan något land som vi kan kalla vårt eget. Det är hög tid att vi slår oss ned.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_22a' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vår modiga Nybyggare väntar på din befallning. Vi borde grunda vår första stad här.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_3_ALTV2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Från det här fröet till stad ska ett imperium växa fram. Men för att staden verkligen ska frodas måste vi först se till våra undersåtars behov.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_23' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The lands before us offer untold riches and dangers.  You must consider that carefully when choosing their final destination.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_36' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Även om staden är lite nu, så kommer den fortsätta att växa om du tillåter det. Stadens och dess invånares öde beror på dig.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_37a' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi har tur att marken som omgärdar vår stad är rik på resurser. Att utveckla den kommer vara nyckeln till vår överlevnad...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_38' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi kan skatta oss lyckliga att vi har så rika marker innanför vår gräns. Men glöm inte att en civilisation består av människor, inte bara mark.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_46_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Så rika marker som dessa kommer säkert uppmärksammas av de barbarer som härjar i området. Vi måste vara beredda att slå tillbaka om vi ska kunna överleva.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_5_ALT_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vår stad behöver Krigare.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_51a' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Om vårt folk ska kunna överleva i det här området måste vi fokusera deras ansträngningar. Bara då kan vi bemästra världen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_6ALTV_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vårt folks säkerhet är vårt viktigaste bekymmer. Instruera din stad att skapa en Krigare.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_61' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utbildningen av den nya enheten har påbörjats. Vårt folk känner sig redan säkrare.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_62' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vårt imperium kommer inte byggas över en natt. Vi har gjort allt vi kan göra den här dagen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_63' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are no other matters for you to attend to.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_7ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utbildningen av våra Krigare fortsätter. Men om vi ska bli någonting mer än de barbarstammar som ansätter oss måste vi också utvecklas på andra sätt.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_71' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det finns de bland oss som har intellektet att låsa upp världens hemligheter. Vi behöver bara vägleda dem.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_8ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utmärkt. När vårt folks förståelse av jorden ökar, så ökas också vår förmåga att utnyttja dess rikedomar och öka vår produktionskapacitet. Vi måste ge dem tid att göra sitt arbete.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_81' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are no more matters requiring your attention today.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_9ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Barbarer närmar sig vår stad! Vi är säkert ett för begärligt mål för att de bara ska ignorera oss.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_92' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi kan inte tillåta dessa vildar att plundra och förstöra allt som vi har byggt. Våra Krigare har slutfört sin utbildning. Låt oss skicka ut dem i strid!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_94' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Krigare är den klinga med vilken vi kommer slå ned vår fiende. De behöver bara vårt handlag för att vägleda dem.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_10ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Seger! Barbarerna har lärt sig att vi inte är att leka med. Men de kommer att återvända, och nästa gång befarar jag att de kommer ta oss på större allvar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_12ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi borde dra nytta av det här uppehållet i fientligheterna. Nu när våra Krigare är förberedda så kan vi växla över vår produktionskapacitet till staden själv.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_121' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utmärkt. De färdigheter som Byggaren kommer få kommer att förbättra vår civilisation rejält.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_13ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Marken som omger vår stad är bördig. Men just nu är den outvecklad. Vi måste skapa en arbetsstyrka om vi ska kunna göra det mesta av resurserna innanför våra gränser.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_131' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have no more matters that require your attention today.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_14_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi får inte glömma bort världen bortanför våra gränser medan Byggarna utbildas för att förbättra livet innanför dem. Det enda sättet att verkligen bemästra den här världen är att förstå den.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_15ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>I tillägg till strid fungerar våra Krigare också som utmärkta utforskare i den här osäkra och fientliga världen. Du behöver bara säga till, så kommer de ge sig ut i det okända.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_151' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vildmarken skulle vara ansträngande för våra trupper att traversera när de ger sig ut ensamma och till fots. Kanske finns det en jämnare väg…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_153' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Våra Krigares ansträngningar bär redan frukt. De har upptäckt en liten Stamby.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_154' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>De här byborna verkar vänligare än de barbarstammar som vi har stött på hittills. Kanske vi borde ta kontakt istället för att attackera dem.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_155' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have attended to all matters necessary today.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_FTUE_47_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Våra krigare står framför byns portar. De väntar på ditt kommando att gå in.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_16_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det verkar som att vänskap har sina fördelar. Ryktet om våra framgångar mot barbarerna har nått fram till den här byn. Imponerade som de är av vår kultur bestämmer de sig för att resa sig mot sina förtryckare och förena sig med oss i kampen mot horden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_17_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Även om de saknar färdighet i strid har den här stammen ändå stor kunskap om vildmarken. Deras förmåga att röra sig snabbt genom terrängen gör dem till idealiska Spejare. Vi borde se till att dra nytta av det.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_171' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There may be other like-minded settlements in the lands ahead.  We would be wise to seek them out in the future...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_18_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi bör använda de här Spejarna med försiktighet. De är utmärkta utforskare, men dåliga kämpar. Det vore klokt att låta dem undvika strid om möjligt.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_181' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>No other matters require your attention today.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_21_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utforskning kan ge många belöningar, men låt oss inte glömma vår huvudstads säkerhet. Vi borde skicka hem våra Krigare för att skydda staden.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_22_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Våra Spejare väntar på instruktioner. De måste utforska och lära oss om nya områden som ännu inte upptäckts.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_23_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det finns inga fler ärenden som måste hanteras i dag.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_231' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our people are hard at work fulfilling your orders.  Let us take this time to further advance our Scouts.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_232' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>No other matters require your attention today.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_26_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Våra invånare gläds åt våra modiga Krigares återkomst. Kanske de borde befästa sin position för att försvara sig mot hotet från barbarerna.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_261' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utmärkt. Med våra Krigare förskansade i sin position är våra invånare säkra. Det vore klokt att behålla den här fördelen så länge det är möjligt.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_24_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Medan våra trupper förbereder stadens försvar har våra främsta tänkare upptäckt hur man extraherar värdefulla resurser ur jorden. Med ett överflöd av värdefull Sten i närheten, skulle våra Byggare kunna använda den här kunskapen när de är klara med sin träning.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_241' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vårt folk finner nöje i att söka kunskap. Vi behöver bara peka ut riktningen för deras ansträngningar, så kommer de avslöja ytterligare ett av världens mysterier.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_242' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Ett klokt beslut. Vårt folk kan nu upptäcka nya användningsområden för de ämnen som vi bryter i våra Gruvor och Stenbrott.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_243' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Men låt oss inte glömma bort vår Spejares utforskning. Det finns en hel värld för oss att upptäcka.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_19_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Låt oss vända blicken mot vår huvudstad medan våra Spejare fortsätter sin upptäcksresa. Allt eftersom staden växer, så växer också hungern i våra invånares magar…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_191' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Våra Byggare står nu redo. Att konstruera en Bondgård på bördig mark innanför stadsgränsen kommer öka avkastningen och ge mer mat till vår befolkning.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_192' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Den här Slätten har rik mylla. Ett perfekt ställe att plantera våra första grödor…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_193' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utmärkt. Med sina magar fulla trivs vårt folk, och befolkningsmängden kan öka…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_194' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Men kom ihåg, Byggarna har inte obegränsat med styrka. Vi bör se till att använda deras förmågor på bästa sätt innan vi kör slut på dem.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_20_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Med deras grundläggande behov tillgodosedda, kan vårt folk nu konstruera mer avancerade strukturer. Kanske ett Monument över allt som de har uträttat skulle inspirera dem att utvecklas ännu mer?…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_201' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utmärkt. När vårt folks stolthet över sin egen kultur växer kommer de sprida vår civilisation bortom våra nuvarande gränser.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_202' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Och följa i våra modiga Spejares fotspår.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_204' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Nu när vårt folk fått mat, låt oss rikta våra Byggares uppmärksamhet någon annanstans. Det finns värdefulla resurser kring vår stad som vi ännu inte utnyttjat.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_205' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Rikta våra Byggares ansträngningar mot att utvinna dessa värdefulla ämnen.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_206' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Utmärkt. Den Sten som vi utvinner från det här Stenbrottet kommer öka vår produktionsförmåga.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_207' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det verkar som att några av våra undersåtar fortfarande behöver din vägledning…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_209' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Med vårt Stenbrott nu färdigt måste vi rikta våra Byggares uppmärksamhet mot ytterligare andra förbättringar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_2091' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Det finns fortfarande värdefulla marker innanför våra gränser; vi måste vägleda dem med omsorg.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_2092' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Våra undersåtar väntar fortfarande på din befallning.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_27_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We are blessed. This Monument stands as symbol of the accomplishments and determination of our people.  Truly they shall now be inspired to push even further into the lands beyond.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_28_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Perhaps we are now ready to spread our civilization beyond our Capital city. If we do not claim the surrounding territory, others surely will.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_29_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Excellent, these brave Settlers are ready to carry our culture into the unknown. However, it will take some time before they are prepared for the journey that awaits them.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_292' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There are reports of dangerous raiders roaming the lands nearby.  It would be best to keep these Warriors here, seeing to the safety of our Capital.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_30_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our Settlers have finished preparations and await your command. However, the lands before them possess untold dangers.  We must not allow them to go forth without protection...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_301' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Excellent, with our people prepared we must now choose our destination.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_302' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>There is an area rich in resources not far from the Capital.  Let us send our Settlers there.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_31_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Though our Settlers are safe under the protection of our Warriors, our Capital is now defenseless. Without the protection of the military we will most surely become overrun by our enemies.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_311' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Though our Warriors are valiant a proper fighting force must be diversified.  Slingers provide a different style of combat.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_312' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>With knowledge comes opportunity. As our people's understanding of this world grows, new paths present themselves to us...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_33_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Location is critical in founding a new settlement.  We are fortunate to have  discovered such an ideal place.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_331' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Order our people to take root here.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_332' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Well done. Our civilization continues to spread beyond expectation.  In time it may rival even our own Capital.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_34_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Already this new city yearns to grow.  Its people await your guidance.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_35_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have reports of another civilization growing on this continent. It seems we are not the only people competing for control of these lands.</Text>		</Replace>		<!---->		<!--EDIT BELOW-->		<!---->				<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_2_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It would seem we have finally tracked the Barbarian raiders plaguing these lands to their source. We must destroy this stronghold or risk future attacks.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_3_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Still might I advise caution. Though primitive and savage, these Barbarians are fierce warriors and their camp is heavily defended.  To ensure victory we must attack with overwhelming force.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_4_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vår stad fortsätter blomstra. Vårt folk frodas, och befolkningen växer!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_5_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Although our scientists would be willing to explore other topics of research, perhaps it is not wise to  distract them from their current work unless absolutely necessary.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_6_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The task at hand is of critical importance. Might I advise patience in this matter. We should allow our people to continue their work if at all possible.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_7_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have spotted another friendly village nearby. Perhaps we should send a Scout to investigate.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_8_ALT2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>A good city can become a great city through careful planning. Deciding where to place a city district is an important decision. Be sure to pick a location best suited for the district to reap the most benefit.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_38_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our legacy will one day be recorded beyond the spoken word.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_381' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>It appears our Slingers have completed their training. Already the people of our city feel safer...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_382' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>As our army continues to diversify and improve, our future grows even more secure.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_383' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>With our Slingers training complete, we may now direct our people's efforts to new pursuits.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_384' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our people still await your command.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_39_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>With Writing we unify our people.  A common written language allows ideas to flourish and our collective knowledge to grow. Were we to provide a place to collect and share this knowledge our people would surely prosper...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_391' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>By concentrating like minds and resources into districts we specialize the growth of our city. We must choose the location of these districts carefully in order to reap the most benefit.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_40_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Already the greatest minds in our civilization eagerly await the completion of this Campus...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_401' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>But we must not allow these great thinkers to be idle.  Let us turn their attention elsewhere...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_41_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our greatest scholars and scientists already begin to gather at our Campus. Providing them with a Library would further assist them in their pursuits.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_END_SCRIPTED_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our people have prospered under your guidance.  Truly our civilization has no equal.  Perhaps now is the time for you to prove this to be true.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_END_SCRIPTED_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The task before us is great, but under your leadership we shall not fail.  As always I stand ready at your side should you require any assistance along the way.  May our civilization truly stand forever.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_END_SCRIPTED_3' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We are victorious! You are now ready to take on bigger challenges, explore new worlds, meet new civilizations, and to achieve victory on your own terms.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_42_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Resources and land are not infinite. It seems we now have competition.  As we do not yet know the true intention of this people, might I suggest we proceed with caution.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_43_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>War is upon us!  Our people are in danger.  We must mobilize an army immediately or risk being conquered.  There is no time for delay!</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_44_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vårt folk frodas verkligen under din vägledning. Men allt eftersom vår civilisation växer, måste vårt ledarskap också utvecklas.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_441' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Vi måste nu bestämma politiska inriktningar för att bättre styra vårt folks tillväxt…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_45_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Disciplin är varje armés ryggrad, och en värdefull fördel över det oorganiserade barbarpacket. Stadsplanering kommer bara göra våra städer mer organiserade och effektiva. Jag föreslår att vi antar båda dessa politiska inriktningar.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_453' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Though our policies begin to bear fruit our civilization will only continue to grow.  We must plan for the future...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_48' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Our people have looked to the heavens, and begun to wonder if our fortunes may be guided by the hands of a greater power. Who are these great gods, and what blessings might they bestow upon us?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_50_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Your inspiration is contagious.  Though our civilization achieves greatness under your leadership, one amongst our people truly shines above all others. Under your guidance shall their impact truly reverberate throughout history.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_51_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Isolation is not the key to prosperity. These traders allow us to reach out to our neighbors. Through trade, we stand to boost our economy, and gain new insights into the mysteries of the world.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_52_ALT' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have made contact with people more advanced than the Tribal Villagers who have aided us in the past. Should we extend the hand of friendship or look to conquer them?</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_WONDER_73' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>The beauty and majesty of this world is sometimes enough to inspire our people to new directions of thought. This was a fortunate discovery...</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_POP_HUT_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>Again our brave Scouts prove their worth to our people.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_GENERAL_1' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>May I make a suggestion…</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_FTUE_GENERAL_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>As you wish.</Text>		</Replace>		<Replace Tag='ADVISOR_LINE_7_ALT_2' Language='sv_SE'>			<Text>We have spotted another friendly village nearby. Perhaps we should send a Scout to investigate.</Text>		</Replace>	</LocalizedText></GameData>